Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. 16mm Microfilm As-Broadcast Scripts, 1928-1958
The John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
J. Walter Thompson Company. 16mm Microfilm As-Broadcast Scripts 1928-1958
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University
J. Walter Thompson Company.
3.0 Linear Feet 292 Items
Founded in 1864, the J. Walter Thompson Company (JWT) is one of the oldest and largest enduring advertising agencies in the United States.
The J. Walter Thompson Company (JWT) 16mm Microfilm As-Broadcast Scripts span the years 1928-1958 and contain transcripts of radio and television dramas and variety shows, news programs, commercials, and sports programming. Companies featured include Andrew Jergens, Ballantine, Brillo, Ciba-Geigy, Fannie Farmer, Ford, General Cigar, J.B. Williams, Kodak, Kraft, Lamont-Corliss (Pond's), the New York Yankees, Penick & Ford (Br'er Rabbit), Standard Brands, the U.S. Marine Corps, and Wrigley. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The J. Walter Thompson Company. 16mm Microfilm As-Broadcast Scripts were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 1987.
Collection Overview
The J. Walter Thompson Company (JWT) 16mm Microfilm As-Broadcast Scripts span the years 1928-1958 and contain transcripts of radio and television dramas and variety shows, news programs, commercials, and sports programming. Companies featured include Andrew Jergens, Ballantine, Brillo, Ciba-Geigy, Fannie Farmer, Ford, General Cigar, J.B. Williams, Kodak, Kraft, Lamont-Corliss (Pond's), the New York Yankees, Penick & Ford (Br'er Rabbit), Standard Brands, the U.S. Marine Corps, and Wrigley.
Collection Arrangement
Arranged by reel number, and physical sequence of the scripts therein. Original documents were microfilmed in no order, so scripts relating to a particular client or program are scattered throughout the collection. The collection described here represents a portion of the whole 16mm microfilm collection.
Subject Headings
These are searchable subject entries for this collection. Performing a search on these subjects in the Duke University Libraries online catalog will bring up other related research materials.
J. Walter Thompson Company
Andrew Jergens Company (Cincinnati, Ohio)
Chesebrough-Pond's.
CIBA-GEIGY Corporation
Eastman Kodak Company
Ford Motor Company
General Cigar Company (Philadelphia, Pa.)
J.B. Williams Co
Kraft Foods Company
New York Yankees (Baseball team)
P. Ballantine & Sons
Penick & Ford, Ltd
Standard Brands Incorporated
United States. Marine Corps
Wm. Wrigley Jr. Company
Advertising
Advertising -- United States
Advertising -- United States -- History
Advertising agencies
Advertising agencies -- United States
Advertising agencies -- United States -- History
Radio advertising
Radio advertising -- United States
Radio advertising -- United States -- History
Radio broadcasting
Radio broadcasting -- 1920-1930
Radio broadcasting -- 1930-1940
Radio broadcasting -- 1940-1950
Radio broadcasting -- 1950-1960
Radio broadcasting -- United States
Radio broadcasting -- United States -- History
Radio broadcasting -- United States -- History -- 20th century..
Radio broadcasting of sports -- United States
Radio advertising
Radio advertising -- United States
Radio advertising -- United States -- History
Radio plays
Radio programs
Radio scripts
Television advertising
Television advertising -- United States
Television advertising -- United States -- History
Television broadcasting
Television broadcasting -- United States
Television broadcasting -- United States -- History
Television broadcasting -- United States -- History -- 20th century..
Television broadcasting of sports -- United States
Television advertising
Television advertising -- United States
Television advertising -- United States -- History
Television programs
Television scripts
Microfilms
John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History
Related Material
Related materials may be found in other collections of the J. Walter Thompson Company Archives:
Carroll Carroll Papers
Dan Seymour Papers
Jack Hilton Papers
John F. Devine Papers
Lois Gaeta Papers
Maury Holland Papers
Description of Collection
- 16mm As-Broadcast Microfilm, 1928-1958
  - Cream of Wheat (Reel 4)
    - Rastus, Cream of Wheat Menagerie, 1929
    - Jolly Bill and Jane, 1929 Jan.-1932 May
    - Jolly Bill and Jane, (continued), 1932 May-Dec. (Reel 5)
    - Jolly Bill and Jane, (continued), 1932 Dec. -1933 Apr. (Reel 6)
    - Angelo Patri, 1931 Aug.-1933 Dec.
    - Angelo Patri, (continued), 1933 Dec.-1934 Apr. (Reel 7)
    - Alexander Woollcott Town Crier, 1934 Oct.-1935 Dec.
      [See reel 34 for Oct. 5, 1935]
    - Buck Rogers, 1936
    - Buck Rogers, (continued), 1936 (Reel 8)
  - B.F. Goodrich
    - Silver Fleet
    - Defiance Tire radio program, 1930
      - Guinevere
      - Geraint and Enid
      - Gareth and Lynette
      - Sir Lancelot
      - Tristan and Isolde
      - Horatius at the Bridge
      - Richard the Lionhearted
      - Don Quixote
      - Joan of Arc
      - William Tell
      - Horatius at the Bridge
    - Uncle Abe and David, 1930-1931
    - Uncle Abe and David (continued), 1930-1931 (Reel 9)
  - Andrew Jergens
    - The Jergens Program
      - Ray Perkins, 1931 June-Dec.
      - Walter Winchell, 1932 Dec., 1933 Sept.-1936 Feb.
      - Walter Winchell (continued), 1935-1936 (Reel 10)
      - Cornelia Otis Skinner, 1935 June-Aug.
    - La Gerardine Program, 1931 Mar. -June, 1933 Feb.-Apr.
  - Odo-ro-no
    - Cutex Program, 1935 June-Aug.
  - Nemoflex, 1931 Mar.-May
  - Davey Tree Surgeons
    - Davey Tree Hour, 1930-1932
  - Richman Brothers Program, 1932 Mar.-June
  - Actin (Boston only), 1931 Dec.-1932 Mar.
  - Vogue Fashion Program, 1931 Apr.-Oct.
  - British Columbia Packers Association (Toronto), 1930 Oct.
  - Reckitt's USA Ltd., 1930-1931
  - Canadian Marconi Program, 1930 Sept.-Dec.
  - Maine Sardines, 1930-1932
  - Maine Sardines, (continued), 1930-1932 (Reel 11)
  - Atlantic Coast Fisheries, 1931-1932
  - Aunt Jemima, 1929-1932
  - Gruen Guild Radio Program, 1930-1931
  - Alexander Wollcott, 1930 Sept.-Dec.
  - Peter's Milk Cocoa (Lamont-Corliss)1929
  - IVC Pearls Homemakers Hour, 1930
  - Corona, How to Write, undated
  - Nestlé Chocolateers, 1930-1931
  - Nestlé Chocolateers, 1931, 1933-1937 (Reel 12)
    [See reel 244 for 1932]
  - Nestlé commercials, 1936-1937
  - Nash Motors, 1934-1937
  - Kops Brothers (corsets), 1934-1935
  - Foremost Dairies, 1930 Apr.-June
  - CeCo dealer program, 1930
  - CeCo dealer program (continued), 1930 (Reel 13)
  - Bromo-Seltzer, 1935-1940
    [See also reel 342]
  - Old Witch radio program, 1929-1930
  - Hathaway Bakeries, Inc.1934-1935
  - S.W. Straus & Co.1930-1932
    - Raltenborn edits the news, undated
  - Standard Brands
    - Fleischmann's yeast for bread
      - Three Bakers, 1932
      - Great Moments in History, 1932-1933
      - Great Moments in History, 1933 (Reel 14)
      - Joe Penner, 1933 Oct.-1935 June
      - Joe Penner, 1934 Dec.-1935 June (Reel 15)
    - Fleischmann's yeast for health
      - Royal Aspic/Vox Pop, 1935 July-Sept.
      - Husbands and Wives, 1936 July-Sept.
      - Dr. Wm. L. Stidger, 1937 Sept.-Dec.
      - Dr. Wm. L. Stidger, 1937 Oct. (Reel 16)
      - All Colored Show, 1937 Apr.-June
      - Werner Jannsen, 1937 July-Sept.
      - Dr. Wm. L. Stidger, 1938 July-Dec.
      - Dr. Wm. L. Stidger, 1938-1939 (Reel 17)
      - Dr. Wm. L. Stidger, 1939 (Reel 18)
      - Dr. Wm. L. Stidger, 1939 Oct.-Dec. (Reel 19)
      - Robert Ripley, 1935-1937
    - Fleischmann's yeast for bread (Reel 20)
      - Robert Ripley, 1936-1937
      - Peg Murray, 1937 Oct.-1938 June
    - Fleischmann's yeast for health
      - Rudy Vallee1930-1932 July
      - Rudy Vallee1932 July-1933 Aug. (Reel 21)
      - Rudy Vallee1933 Aug.-1934 (Reel 22)
      - Rudy Vallee1934 Aug.-1935 July (Reel 23)
      - Rudy Vallee1935 July-1936 Aug. (Reel 24)
      - Rudy Vallee1936 (Reel 25)
        [Missing years 1937-1939; Edgar Bergen first appeared with Rudy Vallee on Dec. 17, 1936]
    - Royal Desserts (Reel 26)
      - I Love a Mystery, 1939
    - Fleischmann's yeast for health
      - I Love a Mystery, 1939
      - I Love a Mystery, 1939 June-Dec. (Reel 27)
      - I Love a Mystery, 1939 Dec.-1942 (Reel 28)
  - Lamont-Corliss/Pond's
    - Those We Love, 1938 Jan.-Feb.
    - Those We Love, 1938 Feb.-1939 Feb. (Reel 29)
    - Those We Love, 1939 Feb.-Mar. (Reel 30)
    - Commercials, 1938-1939
  - Standard Brands
    - Royal Desserts
      - Those We Love, 1939 Oct.-1940 Mar.
    - Royal Baking Powder/Gelatin
      - Martha Deane, 1937 May-Nov.
    - Magic Baking Powder (Canada)
      - Commercials, 1933-1937
      - Commercials, 1937 Feb.-1938 Jan. (Reel 31)
    - Royal Baking Powder (Pacific coast)
      - Talks, 1928 Mar.-Apr.
    - Fleischmann's Food
      - Talks, 1929 Jan.-Apr.
      - Baking industry program, 1931 Oct.
    - Royal Gelatin
      - Audition, 1931
    - Royal yeast cakes (Canada)
      - Commercials, 1934 Feb.-Sept.
    - Royal Baking Powder
      - Martha Deane commercials, 1936 Apr.-Aug.
    - Royal Gelatin
      - Martha Deane commercials, 1936 Apr.-Aug.
    - Fleischmann
      - Commercials, 1937-1940
        [Including Spanish language commercials]
      - Life and Love of Dr. Susan episode 129, 1939 Aug. 14
    - Royal Desserts
      - Commercials, 1932 Jan.-July
      - Commercials, 1932 July-Dec. (Reel 32)
      - Frank Fay, 1936 Apr.-Aug.
  - Skinner Organ, 1930
  - Rand McNally & Co., 1930
  - Simmons, 1931, 1937
  - Peters Shoes, 1931
  - American magazine, 1931
  - Clover Leaf salmon, 1931
  - Pyrex, 1930, 1933
  - U.S. Industrial Alcohol
    - Commercial, 1931
    - Audition script, 1933
  - Tested Products Laboratories, Inc.
    - Placidan, 1934
  - U.S. Gutta Percha Paint Co., 1934 (Reel 33)
  - Florida Citrus Exchange, 1935
  - Enders razors, 1936
  - National Spelling Bee1935
    - Fleischmann's Yeast, 1936 Oct.-Dec.
    - Chase & Sanborn, 1937 Jan.-Mar.
  - Universal Pictures, 1937
  - Hammond Organ
    - Hammond Organ Hour, 1937 Sept.-Dec.
  - Graham-Paige, 1937
  - J.C. Penney, 1937
  - Savings Bank, 1937-1938
  - Burry's, 1938
    [See also reel 150]
  - Zenith Foundation
    - Scientific Investigation of Telepathy and Other Unexplored Powers of the Human Mind, presented by Zenith Radio, 1938
  - Sealtest
    - Legal OK's, 1938
    - Legal OK's, 1938 May-Oct. (Reel 34)
    - James Melton, 1937 Jan.-Oct.
  - Lever Bros. Ltd (Canada) (Reel 35)
    - The Family Man, 1939-1940
  - Wendell L. Willkie
    - Republican campaign, 1940 Sept.-Nov.
  - Kathleen Norris
    - Willkie campaign, 1940 Oct.-Nov.
  - The Circle dramatic scripts (Reel 48)
    [See reels 93, 94, 95 for rest of Chase & Sanborn scripts; reel 156 for rest of Kellogg/Circle scripts; reels 111, 113, 114 for rest of Shell scripts]
    - Accent on Youth (Chase & Sanborn), 1938 Feb.20
    - The Londonderry Air (Chase & Sanborn), 1937 Sept. 19
    - Bad Man (Chase & Sanborn), 1937 Aug. 29
    - Biography (Shell), 1936 Sept. 5
    - Candlelight (Chase & Sanborn), 1937 June 6
    - Call It a Day (Shell), 1936 June 20
    - The Copperhead (Shell), 1935 Aug. 17
    - Coquette (Chase & Sanborn), 1938 Nov. 6
    - The Curtain Rises (Chase & Sanborn), 1938 Oct. 16
    - Cyrano de Bergerac (Shell), 1935 May 25
    - Death Takes a Holiday (Kellogg/Circle)1939 Mar. 26
      [See reel 156 for rest of Malerme]
    - Green Goddess (Shell), 1935 Aug. 31
    - Holiday (Chase & Sanborn), 1938 Feb. 27
    - Is Zat So? (Shell), 1935 Sept. 21
    - June Moon (Shell), 1936 May 2
    - Just Suppose (Shell), 1935 Aug. 31
    - The Last Mile (Shell), 1935 Oct. 26
    - Let Us Be Gay (Chase & Sanborn), 1938 Sept. 25
    - Monkey's Paw (Kellogg/Circle)1939 Apr. 2
    - Mrs. Moonlight (Shell), 1936 Apr. 18
    - Napoleon's Barber (Shell), 1935 Dec. 14
    - Old Lady Shows Her Medals (Chase & Sanborn), 1935 June 20
    - Rip Van Winkle (Shell), 1935 Dec. 7
    - Romantic Young Lady (Chase & Sanborn), 1937 June 27
    - There's Always Juliet (Chase & Sanborn), 1938 Oct. 30
    - You and I (Chase & Sanborn), 1938 Aug. 14
  - Standard Brands (Reel 84)
    - Chase & Sanborn
      - Musical program, 1929 Sept.-1931 Jan.
    - Rubinoff & Orchestra
      - Maurice Chevalier, 1931 Feb.-June
      - Musical program (coastal stations), 1931 Jan.-1932 Apr.
      - Eddie Cantor, 1931 July-1932 Jan.
      - George Jessel, 1932 Feb.-Mar.
      - George Jessel, (continued), 1932 Mar.-Apr. (Reel 89)
      - Burns & Allen, 1932 Apr. 24
      - Harry Richman, 1932 May-Sept.
      - Georgie Price, 1932 Aug. 7
      - Georgie Price and the Revelers, 1932 sept.-Oct.
      - Eddie Cantor, 1932 Oct.-Dec.
    - Benny Kreuger & Orchestra
      - Georgie Price, 1932 May 19
      - Georgie Price, (continued), 1932 June-Dec. (Reel 90)
    - Rubinoff & Orchestra
      - Eddie Cantor, 1933
      - Sims & Bailey, 1933 Apr.-Sept.
        [Bert Lahr and cast]
      - Jimmy Durante, 1933 Sept.
      - Jimmy Durante, (continued), 1933 Sept.-Nov. (Reel 91)
      - Eddie Cantor, 1934 Jan.-Apr.
      - Jimmy Durante, 1934 Apr.-Sept.
      - Jimmy Durante, (continued), 1934 Sept. (Reel 92)
      - Eddie Cantor, 1934 Oct.-Nov.
      - Opera Series, 1934 Dec.
      - Commercials, 1934 Feb.-Dec.
      - Opera Series, 1935 Jan.-Mar.
      - Major Bowes, 1935-1936
      - Major Bowes, (continued), 1936 May-Sept. (Reel 93)
      - A.L. Alexander, Good Will Court, 1936 Sept.-Dec.
      - Haven MacQuarrie, Do You Want To Be an Actor?, 1936 Dec.
      - A.L. Alexander, Good Will Court, 1936 Nov.-Dec.
      - Commercials, 1936
      - Haven MacQuarrie, Do You Want To Be an Actor?, 1937 Jan.-May
      - Edgar Bergen & Charlie McCarthy, 1937 May-Oct.
      - Edgar Bergen & Charlie McCarthy, (continued), 1937 Oct.-Dec. (Reel 94)
      - Commercials, 1937
      - Commercials (Canada), 1937 Sept.-Dec.
      - Edgar Bergen & Charlie McCarthy, 1938 Jan.-May
      - Edgar Bergen & Charlie McCarthy, (continued), 1938 May-Dec. (Reel 95)
      - Commercials, 1938 Jan.-Oct.
      - Commercials, 1938 Oct.-Dec. (Reel 96)
      - Commercials (Canada), 1938 Feb. 10
      - Commercials (French network), 1938 Feb.-Mar.
      - Edgar Bergen & Charlie McCarthy, 1939 Jan.-July
      - Commercials, 1939 July
      - Edgar Bergen & Charlie McCarthy, 1939 July-Dec. (Reel 97)
      - Commercials, 1939 Jan.-June
      - Commercials, 1939 June-Dec. (Reel 98)
      - Commercials (French network), 1939 Jan.-Apr.
      - Edgar Bergen & Charlie McCarthy, 1940 Jan.-June, Sept.-Dec.
        [Off July-August]
      - Commercials, 1940 Jan.-Feb.
      - Edgar Bergen & Charlie McCarthy, 1940 (Reel 99)
      - Commercials, 1940 Feb.-June, Sept.-Dec.
      - Spot announcements, 1940 Mar.-Sept.
      - Springtime & Harvest, 1939-1940
        [Several episodes missing]
      - Commercials, 1939 Oct. 16
      - Springtime & Harvest, 1939 Oct.-1940 June (Reel 100)
      - Commercials, 1939-1940
  - Shell Oil
    - Shell Oil Reporter, 1932 July-Sept.
    - Shell Oil Reporter, 1932 July-Sept., 1933 June-Aug. (Reel 101)
    - Spot announcements, 1933-1937
  - Lever Brothers (Lux) (Reel 102)
    - Peggy Winthrop, 1930-1931 Sept.
    - Peggy Winthrop, 1931 Sept.-Dec. (Reel 103)
      [Many broadcasts missing; see also reel 244]
    - Lux Radio Theatre, 1934-1935 June
    - Lux Radio Theatre, 1935 June-Dec. (Reel 104)
    - Lux Radio Theatre, recording script, 1936 Mar. 18
    - Lux Radio Theatre, audition script, 1936 Mar. 19-20
    - Lux Radio Theatre, 1936 Jan-Mar.
    - Lux Radio Theatre, 1936 Mar.-Nov. (Reel 105)
    - Lux Radio Theatre, 1936 Nov.-1937 Sept. (Reel 106)
    - Lux Radio Theatre, 1937 Oct.-1938 Apr. (Reel 107)
    - Lux Radio Theatre, 1938 May-1939 Jan. (Reel 108)
    - Lux Radio Theatre, 1939 Feb.-Nov. (Reel 109)
    - Lux Radio Theatre, 1939 Nov.-Dec. (Reel 110)
  - Shell Oil
    - Spot announcements, 1937
      [Legal OK's WSYR, Syracuse, N.Y.]
    - Buffalo cut-in commercials, 1936 Mar.-1937 June
    - Football and Sports Review, Eddie Dooley, 1932 Aug.-Dec., 1933 Sept.-Oct.
    - Football and Sports Review, Eddie Dooley, 1933 Oct.-Dec., 1934 Sept.-1935 Mar. (Reel 111)
    - Shell Chateau, 1935 Apr.-Nov.
      [see also reel 48 for dramatic scripts]
    - Shell Chateau, 1935 Nov.-Dec. (Reel 113)
    - Commercials, 1935 June-1936 Dec.
    - Shell Chateau, 1936 Jan.-Sept.
    - Shell Chateau, 1936 Sept.-Dec. (Reel 114)
    - Joe Cook, 1937 Jan.-June (Reel 115)
    - Commercials, 1937 Jan.-June
  - Swift & Co.
    - The Garden Hour, 1931 Feb.-May, 1932 Jan.-May
    - Stebbins Boys, 1931 July-Aug.
    - Stebbins Boys, 1931 Aug.-Dec. (Reel 116)
    - Stebbins Boys, 1931 Dec.-1932 May (Reel 117)
    - Stebbins Boys, 1932 May-Oct. (Reel 118)
    - The Formay Program (Miss Lucy Allen), Happy Ramblers, 1932 Oct.-1934 Apr. (Reel 119)
    - Sigmund Romberg, Wm. Lyon Phelps, 1934 Oct.-1935 Apr.
  - Cream of Wheat (Reel 120)
    - Jolly Bill & Jane, 1933 Mar. 13
      [See reel 6 for rest of script]
    - Sigmund Romberg, 1935 Sept.-Dec.
  - Kraft Cheese
    - Continuities, 1929-1930
    - Kraft Music Hall
      - Paul Whiteman, Al Jolson, Deems Taylor, 1933 June-1934 July
      - Paul Whiteman, Al Jolson, Deems Taylor, 1934 Aug.-Dec. (Reel 121)
      - Commercials, 1934 Sept.-Oct.
      - Paul Whiteman, Al Jolson, Deems Taylor, 1935
      - Jimmy Dorsey, Bing Crosby, 1935 Dec.-1936 Feb.
      - Jimmy Dorsey, Bing Crosby, 1936 (Reel 122)
      - John Trotter Orchestra, Bing Crosby, 1938 Jan.-Mar.
      - John Trotter Orchestra, Bing Crosby, 1938 Mar.-Dec. (Reel 123)
      - Jimmy Dorsey, Bing Crosby, 1937 Jan.-Mar.
      - Jimmy Dorsey, Bing Crosby, 1937 Apr.-July (Reel 124)
      - John Trotter Orchestra, Bing Crosby, 1937 July-Dec., 1939 Jan.-Mar.
        [see reel 127 for Mar. 16 and 23 scripts]
      - John Trotter Orchestra, Bing Crosby, 1939 Mar.-Dec. (Reel 125)
  - Union Central Life Insurance Co.
    - Roses and Drums, 1932 May-Aug.
    - Roses and Drums, 1932 Aug.-Dec. (Reel 126)
      [Oct. 9-Dec. 4, 1932 no scripts--show broadcast from Chicago]
    - Roses and Drums, 1933 Jan.-1934 Feb.
  - Kraft Cheese (Reel 127)
    - Kraft Music Hall
      - John Trotter Orchestra, Bing Crosby, 1939 Mar. 16, 23
  - Union Central Life Insurance Co.
    - Roses and Drums, 1934 Feb.-June, Sept.-Dec.
      [off air during summer]
    - Roses and Drums, 1935 Jan.-Aug. (Reel 130)
    - Roses and Drums, 1635 Aug.-1936 Mar. (Reel 131)
  - Eastman Kodak
    - Kodak Mid-Week Hour, 1930 Apr.-July
    - Kodak Weekend Hour, 1930 Apr.-June
    - Kodak Weekend Hour, 1931 Apr.-Sept.
    - Kodak Weekend Hour, 1932 Apr.-Sept.
    - Kodak Weekend Hour, coastal stations, 1931 Mar.-July
    - Kodak Weekend Hour, coastal stations, 1932 May-Sept.
    - Dr. Haggard, Devils--Drugs--Doctors, 1931 Jan.-1932 Jan. (Reel 132)
    - Angelo Patri, recorded programs, 1934 May-Aug.
      [WTAM, WWJ]
  - Calsodent
    - KPRC Houston, Tex., 1929 July-Aug.
    - WEAF, 1929 May-Aug.
    - WAAT, 1930 Apr.-June
    - Marley R. Sherris, 1930 Mar.-Dec.
    - Robert T. Colwell, 1930 Sept.-Nov.
    - Lewis Dean, 1930 Dec.
    - Marley R. Sherris, 1931-1932 Apr.
    - Marley R. Sherris, 1932 May-1934 July (Reel 133)
    - Bob Howard, 1939
  - P. Ballantine & Sons
    - Tri-City Distributing Co., 1936 Apr.-May, 1938 Feb.-June
  - Black Horse Ale (Canada)
    - Commercials, 1938
  - R.T. French Co. (French's mustard)
    - Commercials, 1934, 1938-1939
  - Sharp & Dohme (Hexylresorcinol)
    - Dr. Howard W. Haggard, 1932 Dec.-1933 May
  - Widlar Products/Standard Brands
    - CW Brand coffee, WTAM, WWJ, 1932
    - CW Brand coffee, WTAM, WWJ, 1937 (Reel 134)
  - Northam Warren (Cutex, Odorono)
    - Phil Harris Orchestra, 1933 June-1934 Dec.
    - Nicla Goodelle, 1935 Sept.-Dec.
    - Spots, 1939 May
  - Lever Brothers (Lux)
    - Life and Love of Dr. Susan, 1939 Feb.-Mar.
      [In this order: production sheet, as-broadcast script, original JWT script before as-broadcast changes]
    - Life and Love of Dr. Susan, 1939 Mar.-July (Reel 135)
    - Life and Love of Dr. Susan, 1939 July-Nov. (Reel 136)
    - Life and Love of Dr. Susan, 1939 Nov.-Dec. (Reel 137)
    - Commercials, 1939
  - Scott Paper Co.
    - Commercials, 1934-1939 Mar.
    - Commercials, 1939 Apr.-Dec. (Reel 139)
  - Colman's mustard
    - Spot announcements, Martha Deane, 1935-1937
    - Spot announcements, WTIC, WLS, WEEI, WSR, WEBC, KSTP, WGY, KDKA, WJAR, 1937
    - Spot announcements, 1939
  - Lamont-Corliss (Pond's creams)
    - Commercials, 1930 Dec.-1931 Dec.
  - City Baking Co. (Rice Bakeries)
    - Baltimore and Washington, 1930-1939
      [incomplete series]
  - Swift & Co.
    - Program, 1936 Jan.-May
    - Program, 1936 May-June (Reel 140)
  - Standard Brands
    - Royal Desserts
      - Commercials, 1933-1934
      - Mary Pickford, 1935 Jan.-Mar.
    - Fleischmann's yeast for bread
      - Three Bakers, 1931
    - Magic Baking Powder (Canada) (Reel 141)
      - Commercials, 1938
    - Chase & Sanborn
      - Orchestra, etc., 1933 Apr.-Sept., 1934 May-Sept.
      - Mrs. Annie Longworth Wallingford, 1936 Feb.-May
      - One Man's Family, 1937 Jan.-Mar.
      - One Man's Family, 1937 Mar.-1938 Mar. (Reel 142)
      - Commercials, 1937
      - One Man's Family, 1938 Mar.-Dec. (Reel 143)
      - Commercials, coastal stations, 1938
      - Commercials, French network, 1938
      - Commercials, Canada, 1938
      - One Man's Family, 1938 Dec. (Reel 148)
      - Commercials, Philadelphia, Providence, Washington, 1938 May-Oct.
      - One Man's Family, 1939
      - Commercials, 1939 Jan.-July
      - One Man's Family, 1939 (Reel 149)
      - Commercials, 1939 July-Dec.
  - General Cigars
    - Robert Burns Panatela
      - Burns & Allen, 1932 Feb.-1933 May
    - White Owl cigars
      - Burns & Allen, 1933 May-1934 Mar.
  - Chateau Haut Briou wine
    - Broadcast, 1933 Dec. 27
  - White Owl cigars (Reel 150)
    - Broadcast, 1934 Mar.-1935 Sept.
  - Burry Biscuit Co.
    - Commercials, 1938 July-Sept.
      [Incomplete; see also reel 33]
  - W.F. Young, Inc. (Absorbine Jr.)
    - Commercials, 1938 June 3
  - General Cigar (White Owl Cigars) (Reel 153)
    - Sports Program, 1939 Oct.-Dec.
  - Lever Brothers (Lux)
    - Lux Radio Theatre, 1938 Nov.
      [See also reels 107, 108]
  - Seeck & Kade (Pertussin)
    - Commercials, 1939 Nov.
  - J.B. Williams
    - Aqua Velva
      - Commercials, 1939 Sept.-Oct.
    - Williams shaving cream
      - True or False, Dr. Harry Hagen, 1938-1939
    - Glider
      - Sports Program, A.B McGinley, WTIC, 1938 Apr.-Sept.
      - Bob Howard, 1938
      - Swing Program, 1938 Apr.-1939 Feb.
    - Swing Program, Bob Howard, 1939 Mar.-Oct. (Reel 154)
  - Elgin National Watch Co.
    - Football Revue, 1936 May-Dec.
      [Incomplete series]
    - Recording of 75th Anniversary Celebration at World's Fair, 1939 Aug. 18
  - Johns-Manville Co.
    - Floyd Gibbons, 1933 Oct.-1935 June
    - Floyd Gibbons, 1935 June-July (Reel 155)
    - Dramatic, 1936 Jan. 13
    - Institutional radio talks, 1937
  - Penick & Ford
    - Vermont Maid syrup
      - Vermont Lumberjacks, 1931-1932 Mar.
        [some scripts by Eleanor Norton]